Heat. Heat.
[music]
Wow.
>> [music]
[bell]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
>> Hey,
hey,
hey.
Hello everyone.
Coma.
Oh, wait. I mean, Ohio.
[laughter]
Yeah, it's Ohio.
Oh, yeah. Hello everyone. How's everyone
been doing?
Hello. Hello.
Yeah. Bye. [laughter]
It's already
new year, a new year for us all.
about
one second.
Uh yeah, today's stream will be a short
one because I have to go somewhere
before 200 p.m.
I have to
go somewhere before 2:00 p.m. So, uh
this will be a short stream.
I just wanted to do a gorilla stream cuz
I didn't know what to do. Uh cuz the
time there's like a time limitation,
right? So sure. Last time uh we did the
collab stream. I said that I will do a
stream later that day, but I couldn't. I
was feeling so tired, so I slept off.
I just rested
more.
But I just rested that day.
So I was feeling so tired.
Okay, give me a minute. Let me just um
see if anything is wrong with the stream
so I could fix it.
Um and if you are able to
uh if you notice that any of the streams
are not working. such as um what do you
call it such as uh Twitch or kick or
even YouTube do feel free feel free to
let me know quickly as possible so I can
like go there and fix it in a
hi
first of all
Happy new year.
Hi. [clears throat]
Um,
so yeah, it's a new year. Uh so this
year I only have two months left. I mean
if you count this month and I don't know
if you count from the next months next
two months then yeah I have only till
March for myself before.
Hi [laughter]
Uh, where is my YouTube stream dying?
there.
Uh
no
again.
[laughter]
So then
so yeah for uh for
um
so uh since I only have three or two
months left before I go to Japan um I
will like to make use of this two three
months
really enjoy myself and yeah have fun
and also Hope I can meet more Japanese
uh people so I can talk and practice
Japanese.
[laughter and gasps]
Hey,
goodbye.
So, yeah. So, that's why I was like,
yeah, I hope I can meet uh more people I
can talk with, play games with,
and stuff
this year. [laughter]
And um yeah,
um I will try my best to do vlogs and
stuff from Japan.
Uh for for your coming. Hi. [laughter]
Me too. Me too. I hope everything goes
well. I'll get my uh the information of
if I am eligible for COE
by February
14th or
something. around February. I will next
month I will know.
I really really hope everything goes
well. So
Tender, hello. Thank you for the hydrate
and stretch reminder. Thank you. Thank
you.
Thank you. Thank you.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, but my uh my throat is already
dry. I don't know why.
So, for today, I thought of just talking
with everyone.
I thought of just talking with you guys.
We'll just chat and stuff. Okay.
Yeah.
Show the name. We'll just chitchat.
[laughter]
Small chithat.
Wait. Uh,
what is today's
uh Oh, it's not here.
Okay, it's done.
total. Okay. Where
uh my exam is on for 18th of
um
18th of um January.
The Q.
She
wait.
No, she can't. Yeah. Go.
[laughter]
Yeah. Oh my god.
Okay.
Uh,
wait. Not here.
Oh my god. What?
My systems are breaking.
Um, you know, it takes me 20 minutes to
set up a stream
like it like none there. Uh, uh, uh, I
was about to say Hindi
like mix it with Hindi, Hindi and
Japanese like [gasps]
Oh my god.
Uh
but yeah. Um
wait, it's not here. N. Okay. Okay.
EB69.
Okay. Okay. It's here. It's here. Hi.
Hi.
I see you. D. I see you. I see you.
Uh [groaning]
Sammy,
I got it. I got it. I got it.
Hello and happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Kuranosan.
How's the birthday boy doing?
Exams over. Uh, I skipped all of my
exams.
I skipped all of my exams.
That's a different story. I'll I'll I'll
talk about it someday. I skipped all of
my exams. Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, don't do that window.
[laughter]
[gasps]
So yeah. Um, today will be a just chat.
I also wanted to do a singing practice
thingy wrench thingy cuz a friend of
mine dragged me to do a cover duet cover
for that chain man song Jane Do. Uh so I
have to learn the male lines for it. But
I went I'm I'm with the female lines. Uh
the main lines a bit uh hard for me. So
I have to practice that. So recently
uh I was listening to that song
and also also um today is third of
January.
Um
I believe I will uh upload the video by
5th kana or tomorrow itself.
H
uh yeah, there will be a video talking
about my model situation. I wanted to
make that video then if possible like um
use my live 2D model again for a bit.
Ah,
[laughter]
thank you for becoming a member. Welcome
to the Astra constellation.
Thank you. Thank you. Hello.
[laughter]
Nice. Nice. Hi. So, uh, I
I I got rid of my courage, you know, to
use my
my usual life to the model.
Um,
cuz, uh, again, uh, if things happen, if
anything happens,
then it is what it is. But so far, I
don't see any going to happen for a
while. So I'm going to use my old model
which I've been using for for like four
two three four years right [laughter]
so from next three months I'll do that I
guess I mean I can just switch over to
the other model right now but yeah I
feel like it's very better if I can get
my video out
uh so then it's better
uh
Hi. Hello.
Happy new year. Hello, Yasu. Hello.
Hello. Happy New Year. Hello. Welcome to
my stream.
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
This year is going to be fun. [laughter]
I can feel it.
It has to be fun. It must be. Yeah.
Also, I made a video
u looking back on how my 2025 went. So,
if you haven't watched it, feel free to
watch it. It's on my YouTube
channel.
I'm scared of this year. Sunday.
New year, new you. New me.
You got this.
Face your obstacles. Dio. Don't run
away.
Yeah, you got to face them. [laughter]
Oh.
Um.
Uh, I haven't uh like announced on
Discord that I'm live now. Let me just
do that real quick.
Um, I have to wait
20 minutes for a YouTube live stream to
be logged into my database.
It's annoying there.
I have to wait for 20 minutes.
cuz uh it has to run through like five
checks. No, it's crazy.
Ah, it's not responding there.
Oh my god.
Also, also mate, I wanted to ask, is my
stream audio setup really bad? like do I
sound too loud sometimes and stuff? I
heard some feedback.
Um,
and also I noticed it myself too. My mic
sometimes speaks, right?
Yeah, I I I've been noticing it
sometimes, too. My mic does speak
sometimes.
It's good enough. H I think it's
recognizable when I play a game.
I hope I'm not too loud when I'm doing
game streams. I not this on the Arator
stream. Uh the game was too loud.
Uh the game was too loud. So
last time
I'll fix that time. No worries.
My PC is dying. D I can't do anything.
It's stuck. Am I live? Oh my god. No.
Don't do this to me. [gasps]
Oh my god. Don't do this to me.
How do I get a Hi. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
You have a PC? I don't have one.
[laughter]
I have a PC. I'm waiting for my um this
thing this
[laughter]
Yeah, this is the year I will be
suffering in Japan. But I'm going to
enjoy my enjoy my I'll enjoy and learn
the trial and error now.
Yeah, this year can't wait.
[laughter and gasps]
I'm going to do my best to reach out to
more Japanese YouTubers who will be
willing to like, you know, hang out with
me or play games with me so I can like
have someone to talk and practice
Japanese.
So,
that'll be nice. So, I can like
understand what's going in their head
and everything.
You're in Japan? No, I will be in 3
months. Uh, by April. I will be in after
April. Yeah, by April. Yeah, by April.
Uh, by April. Oh, by April, I will be
there.
Hi. Uh, okay. Let me try to fix this so
I can like um continue on with the
stream. Okay.
Uh, I'll have to fix up my backend
systems.
Yeah. So, what happens is now when I
schedule a stream on YouTube, it takes
up to um it takes up to 10 minutes. I
mean, it takes up to 1 second to fetch
all the streams from YouTube API. Then
it has to like map each and every single
thing. No. Yeah. Yeah. takes up to 10
minutes because it has to check from the
internal files like I have a two files
one is the main registry and other is
the stream
yeah it checks checks checks sees if
it's upcoming or not all those stuff
takes around 10 [music] 20 minutes I
have to cut it short somehow
so uh in cases like this today's stream
now I schedule my stream out of nowhere
like 10 minutes before [laughter]
and just went live. I I could I can't
like situation right now is I cannot uh
announce that I'm live on Discord cuz I
could do it manually but I have my
automated setup now. I have to wait for
it to send the message. [laughter]
Yeah. Bye. You live alone or with
family? With family. With family. But
this is like my office space for Jockn.
I call it my Jocknik HQ.
Uh but I'll also have one day wish to
have my own uh place in Japan once I'm
settled there.
Yeah, speaking of which, by next month I
have to uh either work on my logo stuff
or just make like an acrylic glass panel
for my door stuff
cuz it's like an um establishment,
right? This space. So, I have to like
make like a I have like a flex board
which says doc and like address and uh
GST number. I have to change it just to
keep it like a logo thingy. Um, I don't
think GSD people will do their in-house
inspection anymore. So, I can like uh
change it to a logo format.
So, I'll do that.
Yeah, my dad has been telling me you
could make it into a glass thingy like
how my how like like our um the next
door is like a law foam so they did like
a glass panel thingy. Uh it's really
nice.
Yeah, it's really nice.
Uh
Yes.
Hi. Uh, let's check.
Bro, it's not Lori King.
line.
Oh my god. I'm going to
Is his stream buff? Oh. Oh my god. Is it
buffering?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's buffering.
Nanda, why is it buffering? Why? Why?
Now I see the buffer. That's not
supposed to happen.
Wait.
Oh, my 24x7 channel is running. That's
why. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'll
fix it. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me fix this. Uh,
I'll do something about this 24-hour
channel now this year. Uh before I leave
uh honestly
uh I'll have to manage
some of my problem. Hi. Hi.
Oh god. Uh [groaning]
tada. So yeah, this year I'll try to do
more videos. That's what I'm one one of
the things I'm trying to do. Even though
it's not that good quality and stuff,
but I just wanted to make it like a
personal blog or something for now and
see how that goes.
Um, once we have uh a good resources and
this and that stuff, then we can do more
monologuic stuff, which I wish to do.
Yeah. Yesterday I was watching concert
Kamisubaki concert
uh and man it inspired me so much. I
also want to do concert learn and make
so many stuff and like have my 3D model
and I'm just talking to the camera and
walking with the scenery behind me and
stuff. That is so cool though.
Wow. Okay, I turned the DVR. So if um
the stream is lagging, you will just be
kept on upstream. Got some work to do.
I'll be taking my All the best. See you
later. Hi. Take care. Take care.
Thank you for coming by.
Nihoni
VCI
frustrating.
Oh, I never been in a VC with Japanese
people yet.
I joined the Japanese server, but I'm
scared to join.
Everything is in
shine. I know that
there's that as well. [laughter]
Uh
yeah, there's that as well there.
Me being shy shy.
So
yeah, man. Y
stream up.
It will be when you make Japanese with
your friends. Yeah, I think I'll get
I'll have to get used to it. So,
I will have to get used to it.
Hello Chloe GPT. Welcome. Welcome. We're
just talking. They hold your hand. But
they are just having conversation with
each other. So we it'll be brute force
to evolve. Ah
so yeah
I will have to balance and see how it
goes.
Yeah and this year I got to like uh
change up a lot of things with my
channels especially Twitch and kick
right. I have to work on the panels man.
[laughter]
I have to work on the panels. I have to
update some of the panels.
Like how Pokemon evolves using a stone.
Yeah. Oh my god. Wait, Pokemon's evol.
Wait, that's a thing.
What?
Wow. I didn't know.
Crazy.
I don't get what's wrong with this. Oh
my god.
Yeah, this is why I uh should have
tested before doing my stream. H
yeah, I should have tested before doing
my stream. Yeah,
but it's okay.
It is what it is.
I think I can just
kill this
puzzle like you can capillary in your
brain. Oh,
interesting.
Do we need to know what Jonas or will we
give?
[laughter]
I don't know actually. H good question.
Good question though.
I'm a constellation. Huh? So
h
what do I evolve into?
I'm just uh I mean the next evolution
will be a should I leak it? I don't
know. But yeah,
I'll be a entity.
Um being a constellation, I'll be given
a role.
Uh after that what happens
after that
galaxy? I don't [laughter] know.
I mean h I actually haven't thought much
about the evolution stuff of my lower
stuff.
So
I'm just a constellation
thingy
which some powers and stuff this and
that but I wanted to like like if I were
to bring myself into an anime or
something. No, I don't want to go with
that already overpowered
uh kind of throw up, right? I don't want
to do that.
I want to just be a I want to start from
scratch and then get to get to my power
thingy kind of thingy. That'll be nice.
Oh god, I have to revamp the whole thing
there. [laughter]
Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, that would be nice. No.
Yeah. Like I got chosen to be the next
something or something. Oh my god. Wait.
What the That's a great idea.
Oh, that's really nice.
But it'll be nice honestly
cuz I want my community and my jocknik
lord and everything. No, to be like an
ARPG kind of set setup as in [music]
uh you find the bread bed breadcrumbs
and uh patch it up together to get to
understand a secret story line or hidden
line or something like that. Stuff like
that. But yeah, that would be nice. I
have to like
uh think about
how like all these stuff. No, it'll be
nice honestly. Yeah, I I think I'll
prepare it before the new outfit reveal
stuff happens. Um when I can do that
model outfit reveal it. Yeah, I should I
should prepare everything.
Hope I can.
You already have a story though. Yeah, I
think. Wait, do I Wait, I do. Wait, I
do.
I do.
>> Wait,
wait, I do. I think I have a story. I
forgot. Did I write it on my website or
in the wiki or something? Let me check.
Did I put it in the lower? Oh, wait.
There's a lore section. What? Official
lore is currently TVA. Okay, fine. Okay.
I don't have I didn't put in the thing
yet. Huh.
Can we use in parts anywhere? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. True, true, true. Yes. Yes.
Yes.
So, yes. Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Man, I wish I can demortal,
but yeah, it's expensive.
I'm like
I'm in the lore for I don't want to
document though ah I l stuff
that'll be nice me getting se like in
the fantasy world [laughter]
reincarnated or summoned kind of kind of
throw there
that'll be nice but you see that
everywhere now that's the thing that's
why I don't want to go with that kind of
setting
Yeah,
if I'm going with a setting, I think I
would want to go with a setting where uh
it's like uh
the like not how is it? It's like an
established world setting
like for example,
what is the word? Post a collective
world setting those kind of things,
right? where oh the world is futuristic
and stuff and you exist, you make some
friends, this and that, right? Then some
stress stuff happens. You get into a
messy situation and you have to save the
world or something. [laughter]
That's kind of niceish,
I guess.
I don't know.
So then it h I have to think about it.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz I separated Jockn
next from my um other project. No. So I
can do whatever I want with Jock.
Like whatever uh unique uh like original
story I wish to write for Junk, I can
take my time to do that this time. No.
Yeah.
For the other projects, the characters,
I think I'll go with the fixed wall
setting
and everything. Yeah.
So many stuff, man. [laughter]
So many stuff.
Save them all from I don't know. I just
randomly said it. I I just randomly said
it.
Yeah, I just randomly said it.
It's going to be 11. Nice.
Yeah, today um just it will be just a
chatting stream. I wanted to play
Araters. You know, I haven't touched
that game for like a week now.
Yeah, this week I didn't do anything. I
didn't touch the game at all. I was
watching
other streamers play it, but I have to
get myself and play it now. The only
unlucky moment I situation which happens
is whenever I try to stream it, I really
have a bad luck. I die quickly.
Uh cuz my PC is struggling. No, it's a
heavy a little bit of a heavy game for
my PC. So,
there's that.
No. Uh what? What?
Wait, what? That's explosive. What the?
Uh, no.
What?
[laughter]
Oh my god. Do you think that exists? I I
don't think anyone would do that for
like I mean it will be there for like
bigger people. I I'm like a small
nobody. I don't think
Yeah.
Hi.
[laughter]
You're crazy.
Uh,
am I alive?
Am I live? Am I live?
Okay, I'm back. I'm back. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Yes, I had to terminate it. Okay,
fixed it. Fixed it.
None there.
Ah, you got an ad.
Oh my god.
Twitch is not fine anymore.
I don't know what's happening today.
Could it?
This is so weird.
I think I really have to clean up my
whole PC, man.
It's It's really really struggling. I'm
I'm noticing how
how strong how much it is struggling and
I feel sad about it. [laughter]
Wow.
Crazy.
Okay.
I
It's crazy out here. Wow.
What the
Okay, one second.
If this is the case, how am I?
If this is the case, how will I do this
uh singing practice thingy right now?
Wow.
Oh, wow.
Okay. I hope it's fine now.
Yeah, my browser is lagging. This is
lagging. That is lagging.
Ya ya ya.
At least kick is doing fine.
Kick is working. Nice.
It's good that I have other alternatives
if people are having ads, right? If
you're having ads on YouTube and Twitch,
you can just watch me on kick or beam.
Those have no ads at all.
So you're like options for people.
[laughter]
So there
Yeah.
You know, that's how I'm not able to
send an announcement. I I think I'll
just manually do the announcement, bro.
At this point, I'm I'm like, bro, this
is too much.
It's taking forever to just do uh
uh [sighs] I'll fix it.
Wow. you know, also talking about
backend stuff and Sammy stuff, right?
Uh, next thing I'm going to do is have a
user database for all the viewers,
right? So, what I'm planning to do is
just like in these video games and
stuff, they have this user ID stuff,
right? Like um like a UID system, right?
like that everyone will be assigned the
random
16 digit or 8digit
ID every user account and you that ID
determines your account kind of thingy
locally and your YouTube username,
Twitch username, kick, other platform
usernames. I have to somehow log it
manually I think
or you can do it. I I think I have to
make that set up. Yeah. Yeah. So, every
message will be under one thread this
time rather than multiple threads for
different platform. No, I'm going to
work on that. That's going to help so
much when greeting people and stuff. No.
Um, yeah,
it'll be nice. I will have to work on
that.
So there
finally it's it's finally open. Okay.
Okay. Now I can do the announcement.
There you go. Now I can do the that I'm
live on Discord finally.
Here we go.
[laughter]
It now synced up the whole data.
Yeah. Why? This is so
painful. [laughter]
Yeah. You know what? Next time
um
I'll do something else just to not like
this. like uh if I'm scheduling, I'll
schedule like 1 hour before the stream.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So,
1 hour before the stream. Hi. Anyway, uh
I have a few hours left. So, uh want me
to practice that song? I've been
learning the Jane though.
I thought I breath um
cuz I have like a month left to uh to
study it to like
get it good enough so I can like cover
it.
But I'm struggling with my audio setup,
man.
My audio is really boo.
I have to like use so many post section
post for
effects and everything, I guess,
to get it working the way uh sounding
the way I want.
Like sometimes the mic peaks. No, I hate
that.
Sappy son. Hello.
Happy new year and welcome, welcome,
welcome. Oh yeah, I downloaded Dainci
Resolve
because I got uh I I saw this uh feature
that you can extract subtitles and edit
using subtitles and like it can
automatically ripple delete silences and
stuff. So I was like, "Okay, I'm going
to get it. I'm going to download it.
cuz good features now helps you with um
video stuff.
Yeah, I'm excited to test that out um
later today. I guess I'll be recording
the video. I've been wanting to I said
it in my last train uh video
uh like about the model situation uh my
tragic situation with my model.
[laughter]
So I'll just make a video about it and
then we can like I feel like I can like
start to
h I can like start to like use the old
live 3D. Hello X
Ron Rayon Rayan X- Rion. How do I
pronounce your name? Hello,
welcome.
Welcome. Welcome. How you doing?
It's been a while. No, you came by last
time, I believe. Uh during the with
winds meet stream.
Okay. Hello, Axuin. Right now I remember
how to pronounce your name.
What is the meaning of gorilla? A g a
gorilla stream. Gorilla stream means an
unplanned
stream. Basically,
it's an unplanned stream. Unexpected
unplanned. Don't know what I'm doing
thingy. That's what you put Gelia
again. just search it. Go on Google and
search Gorelia. They'll you'll find a
Reddit post
uh which is for like hol life
terminology and stuff. No, most of the
uh most of the Japanese YouTubers use
this terminology
and that's a video too. I think
yeah, basically it's a sudden stream
without any announcement or anything.
without an announcement, the streamer
goes live and just uh engages with their
audience and everything.
Yeah. Yeah. Like Twitch and stuff.
How in Twitch? No, you just go live
without a schedule. Just go live, start
your stream, chill with your community
and stuff, do stuff like that. Same
thing. But when it comes to YouTube,
usually on YouTube, you'll schedule a
stream, make an announcement that you're
going to stream on this day at this
time, right? So much stuff, right?
Yeah. Think of it like that.
I thought it was gorilla. Did you pass a
Japanese? No. Uh, it's on 18th of
January. that exam.
January 18th is the exam I have to study
and I today I have offline classes at
300 p.m. So I have to wrap the stream up
by like 1:00 p.m. or something and like
uh eat lunch and prepare and then leave.
How many exam? It's just one exam. I was
having exams earlier because of my
university stuff.
I kind of skipped everything. I in a way
I didn't write any of the exams cuz I
was like I'll just focus on one exam
that that's the Japanese exam because
I'm going to Japan now. So I have to
clear it.
But also the university thing if I can
write it from Japan then it's good. It's
not confirmed yet.
I have to like uh it's got oh stuff is
like jail uh NAT it's NAT
it's a NAT exam
uh this
N exam N
yeah so I'll be writing NAT
I'll be writing N Q4
so it's equivalent to GPT
GPT for
uh uh which is equivalent.
Why am I writing in chat?
Equivalent to Jan for
ILts uh exam it expires after some time,
right? NAT doesn't uh JLPT and NAT does
not expire.
The thing is JPT is uh the main thing
but it has exams every twice in a year
two times only two times in a year June
July and December but when it comes to
NAT you can take it every month
a lot of schools nowadays are accepting
NAT exam NAT certifications
so even if you don't have never written
real PT
can still Right. Uh you can go with your
net certificate and you'll get
uh yeah admission and everything.
So
it'll convey you'll get into Japanese.
Not sure though. I mean I already got
I'm I'm already I am selected for the
school.
I'm just worried if I my um visa and
stuff will
uh go well properly this year cuz last
year it it had delayed. No, I was told I
I have to wait till the next intake
that's April 2026.
Yeah, I hope this year at least I can
go. Man, [laughter]
I waited in a year.
Uh
but yeah the thing is now if I go to
Japan if I am there in Japan I don't
think I can stream for six months cuz
school is strict dotory is strict noise
complaint is a thing so many issues
if I get caught
that
if I if someone complains
like yeah you're too loud or you this
guy is strange screaming and yelling and
talking so much at night. We want our
peace or something. If someone
complains, no, I'm dead dead. I
[laughter] don't I don't think I'll be
able to [gasps]
uh
stream stream if I get like a warning
and stuff then I'll have to be careful
cuz if I break the rules, I'll be
deported back to India now, I think.
Yeah, the it's a strict school, man. So,
I have to be careful.
Yeah,
I don't know how it things will be, but
I'll try to at least upload videos or
record videos. Okay, that's the only
thing I'm thinking right now. I'll just
upload videos even if I can't stream.
I love streaming. Honestly, streaming is
fun, honestly.
Go. Um,
give me a minute.
Guide melody line. What is this?
Oh, for university. Uh, for university?
No, I have to just pass my N1 exam, ZPT
from Japan. then I'll be good and I'll
use the connection of the language
school cuz they will help me. It's a
strict school. This school uh looks into
like giving the students higher
education and wherever they want to go
and stuff. No. So I'll try to if
possible try to get into a university
then switch my visa again to study visa
for 3 4 years. Then after I'm done with
the university stuff I have to find a
job and switch to a work visa. all those
stuff.
Yeah, I have the the only good the good
thing I learn is how to manage myself
like financial things and everything
now. So I don't get uh get broke and I
don't get into trouble cuz I am sure
that like if I close my eyes money will
be spent like a [laughter] like water.
You won't realize when money just flies
away because of all the expenses and
stuff. No, the one thing I'll be able to
learn as skill I can get from going to
Japan will be like to manage all these
financial stuff so I don't get myself in
trouble.
Yeah. So there
I just hope I don't get to that point.
Okay, let me check.
Wait a minute. Where? Huh?
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yeah, never mind. He didn't see
anything. Oh, sorry.
I I was switching things around and then
something happened. [gasps]
Yeah. I went to a home to town parted
with my parents parents were outside. Uh
according to my I woke up after two
days. What the heck? What?
Are you okay?
[laughter] Oh my god.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Y
crazy like how
Okay, let's do that kuki thingy. Okay.
Uh let me try to learn the song.
Oh, I forgot. [laughter]
[gasps]
It's not Christmas anymore. So, I don't
think I should use this background.
What the
I'm never drinking. Hi.
Hi. Let's do the song uh singing
practice thingy. Uh because I have to
learn Jane though within a month.
uh for the duet cover.
Yeah.
I hope I can get it right.
Okay.
Everything is lagging.
My PC. Oh my god, I hate it so much.
Oh my god. Okay.
No guide melody. Okay. This one has
guide melody, right? Okay. Okay. Okay.
All right. Shall we do it?
9 1590 lagging. [laughter]
I have a 1660 Super. That's why it's
such a bottleneck.
Yeah,
it is such a bottleneck.
Okay. Um, let me get it.
Uh, where is the
We've all this.
Do you hear the music?
Oh, wait. That's not the one. Sorry. Uh,
[music] this one, right?
I lowered it a bit.
Can you hear the sound? Okay. Wait.
Okay. Uh,
lower it here.
Wait, isn't it better if I can like just
show the
show this version where you see like the
Japanese
stuff. Why is the Wait a minute. I just
realized something.
This is stretched, isn't it? There you
go.
Okay, next. Um,
so if I play it, will it?
Ah, it won't capture. Uh,
Dang it. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I
have an idea. I'll just put it here.
Different new tab. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. And I'll put it like this.
Theater mode. Maybe. No. No. No. Wait.
I'll
not do the zoom.
No, I need the cursor. No. Oh, n. Oh my
god, this is such a hectic.
Okay, I'll just keep my cer over here.
Okay. Okay. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Uh
reverb. Uh, let me check. How do I
sound? Okay. Is it loud? Okay. Okay.
>> Hi.
Hold on. Let's go.
It would be really better if I could
zoom this in or something.
I'm going to do that. All right.
No, that won't work.
I'll just run with it.
It's fine. Hi. 3 2 1
chain though.
Wait,
wait, wait. [laughter]
I was not ready.
What? I was not ready. What? What? Wait,
wait, wait.
I was not ready. Wait. My bad. My bad.
I was not ready. M. Uh,
hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up. Uh,
there you go.
Oh, wait. Uh,
I was not reading chat. One second. Uh,
what song is this? This is the Chainsaw
Man song.
Have you ever seen Takopi's original
song? No, I haven't watched that anime.
Uh, I thought of highlighting or
coloring. The new model is colored.
Don't worry, the new model, the new uh
outfit thingy. Uh, if I can ever afford
to have it.
Uh,
yeah.
I don't know what to say of no sign.
[laughter]
Crazy.
Okay. Thank you for that information.
But yeah. Hi. Let's go. Uh this is a
Chainsaw Man song. Uh the movie song
Jane Do. It's a duet song.
Hi. Uh, can I show
[clears throat]
I need a guiding vocal. Mate, I need the
actual guiding vocal. Wait, hold up.
I can't do this. Uh, I Wait, wait, wait,
wait.
I think I'm singing it wrong.
Okay, I got this all.
Hi. Three, two, one. I have to time it
correctly so I can do this.
Bro, I'm busy. Stop lagging. Let me
think.
Oh my god.
Gau's voice is much deeper. Yeah,
I can't I can't do deeper voice.
I I tried.
I can't. [laughter]
The only way I could do it if I choke
myself, which is bad. Do not do that.
[laughter]
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Hi.
Uh, wait. Do you think I start time to
start? One second. Someone's knocking on
my door.
Oh, never mind. Not not mine. Okay.
Different door. Okay. Uh, I don't smoke.
[laughter]
I don't do those stuff. Why is my PC
lagging, bro? Why is it Is it this bad?
Oh my god. Why What is going on?
I'll just close this.
Uh, get off. Let me stop Steam.
Okay. [clears throat]
Hi. Uh, let me
do it with this one.
Is it moving? Okay. Hi.
Okay. Three, two, one.
Okay, that should work.
And I have to No, the Twitch is fine.
YouTube is bad. Gone. Kick is fine.
YouTube being YouTube.
That's why
I'm switching to Mel for now. I have to
keep this open or else the stream will
cut off every 30 minutes due to the API
stuff.
Oh, okay. It's sending the signal. Nice,
nice, nice. Okay. Nice. Nice.
Let me stream this time peacefully. Oh
god. Hi.
Keep the mic here.
Where did I start?
Fore!
Foreign! Foreign!
Oh, come on.
I made mistakes. [laughter]
Wait. Uh, so this line,
this line,
and
Okay, I'm getting a call. Oh my god. No
one's letting me stream peacefully
today. What the heck?
One second. PR.
Okay, I'm back. I'm back. Oh my god.
Wow.
Okay. Uh so in a way I don't need to
sing the Hikaruan's
uh lines at all for the duet cover. All
I need to do is sing the kenchi is ina
lines which are this much
and this much
only those lines [laughter]
the first two that's it cuz it's a duet
now another was a friend of mine she'll
be doing the hikanch
stuff
hello parasite gaming welcome welcome
hello happy new year welcome Um,
welcome to my stream.
Okay,
we could try with the melody line this
time. Let's go.
[clears throat]
Fore
[singing]
you
Oh my god, I did it.
I messed [laughter] up.
No,
I messed up.
Okay.
Oh,
I He got this. [laughter]
[gasps]
I messed up.
I think it's better to read the Japanese
rather than using the uh Romani
thingy. Oh my god. Ra question. Are you
Indian? Yes, I'm an Indian YouTuber. I
am an Indian YouTuber. Yes,
I am an Indian YouTuber.
Okay. Um, here
you see it's so lagging. No, my PC. Oh
my god. You know what? I'll not do the
cursor zoom mouse zoom in thingy. I'll
just turn it off. Yeah. Yeah. So, you
can see the whole thing as it is. Okay.
All right.
Uh
okay. [clears throat]
I think uh India have a smallest fan
base of YouTubers. Yeah.
Still not uh that much here now.
Okay, let me just do this.
Why was I zoomed in? Okay. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Keep it over there. And
uh Okay. Good. Uh the chorus right
here. I'm I'm also trying to become an
Indian YouTuber. Oh, good luck to you.
Good luck. Good luck.
Good luck. They all
I'm wishing you the best.
I mean there's uh goods and bads with uh
you know being a Indian YouTuber but I
hope you'll
I hope you'll do it better. Don't worry
you got this.
Yeah. I mean one advice I would say
after being meter for like six years now
uh do your own thing. Don't get into a
community or anything. just do your own
thing.
Um there will be people who will
join your boat for your stuff but
in the end they may never be
a good friend or maybe fakes or
something. There'll be haters this and
that. There'll be people telling you you
can't do this and that. But
ignore all the silence and just follow
what you're passionate about. If you
want to do Vubing, if you want to try
out Viming, go for it.
Um, you slowly slowly
uh learn how to do content creation and
live streaming and making content, all
those stuff. It's a journey. No. Yeah,
we got this.
Don't let anyone else tell you
otherwise. Go for it.
All right.
Uh, okay. One second.
I'm do this. Go.
Oh my god.
Why is it hard to pronounce that? Is it
because I'm following the English one?
Oh my god.
Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Okay, we'll start from the beginning.
First lines go.
Thanks D. But I don't want to be a
traditional one like doing only live
stream. I'll find a new route I'll give
Indian and new YouTubers. Oh, go for it.
I mean uh Vubing doesn't mean always
live streaming, you know. [snorts] Uh
live stream a YouTuber who live streams
is technically known as a V streamer.
YouTubers are
uh someone who also wakes I mean I mean
it has a different meanings but yeah you
can do videos and stuff no yeah yeah go
for that if you want to
my previous advice was that just uh
don't get yourself into drama this and
that and everything right there will be
people who would do stuff to bring you
down and everything as someone who went
through it. So yeah, that's the only
thing. Don't let your creativity be
[snorts]
uh ruined by just because of others
jealousy and stuff. Yeah, that's what I
meant in my previous advice thingy.
Yeah, especially because uh Indian meing
is like really really niche.
Only a few people do. I mean there are a
lot of people who do it around 300 PE
metubers are there in India but still
um yeah
it's a small thing community wise and
everything it's a small thing now
I just want your perspective
yeah my thing is like I love ETF
it is really fun I mean I come from a
live streaming first kind of thingy.
Uh, but I do want to dabble into video
content creation like a video making
stuff and everything. [snorts]
Yeah, it is fun like using a medium to
make content and just do your own thing
and everything.
Yeah.
And I'm really passionate about tubing,
man. Other I would have quit already.
Um Yeah.
But it is hard but also it is nice.
Yeah. But I would say
do your own research if possible.
There's a lot of guides, a lot of
resources out there. If there's anything
you are having difficulties when it
comes to YouTubing and stuff, let it be
like if you're going to uh like to make
just videos and stuff. No, there too.
Just so you know uh all the
stuff there. Yeah.
[sighs]
One advice would be just don't get on
Twitter. [laughter]
Twitter is crazy.
Yeah, I mean Twitter is the only way you
can get
the al algorithm or like networking and
stuff happens.
But yeah, it has it good size and bad
size.
That's the thing.
Wait, wait a minute. The reverb was not
active. Wait, it is act. div. What the
what?
What?
Check. Okay, now it's there.
Are setting up all the things my avatar
set up. Oh, nice. Nice. Good for you.
Good for you.
Enough.
Yeah, there's like free avatars you can
try before investing into YouTubing your
own original character and everything.
No, before spending like two, three
lakhs on a model and stuff, try out the
free ones and see if it ifing is
something you would like to continue or
not.
Yeah,
that's my advice to any newcomers.
Uh
that's my advice to any newcomers
cuz it is hard.
Yeah.
Some people just get in and and
suffocate.
You don't want that
on mobile. Oh. Oh, you do it on mobile.
Oh, you know.
Oh, you're using that one. Oh, I know
that model. I know that model. Yeah,
it's from Bhna. It's a good model,
actually.
Me, too. Yeah. Yeah, I know that one.
Oh, nice.
Ah, cool. Cool.
Uh, if you want to record stuff from
phone, no, just get the V Studio mobile
app. Get the pro version or something so
you can use it on PC. If you ever want
to use your phone camera just to track
your model, you can do that.
Yeah,
that's nice.
>> [gasps]
>> It's good to see that a lot of newcomers
are coming all every year. That's nice.
That is nice.
Uh, okay. What was I doing again? I
[laughter] forgot.
What's there?
Oh my god.
I can
speech
on
combo.
Did I press something? Uh, did I do
something? Uh,
I did not tie you out or something.
Right. Okay.
Oh, God. Thank you. Oh,
I got scared. Bye-bye.
I I accidentally pressed something and I
singing for [snorts] us. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm learning this song cuz I have
a cover. I have to learn this within a
month cuz there's a cover song I have to
do with a friend. So,
um
What? [laughter]
Mama. Okay.
[laughter]
New you. New Year.
by my show.
Uh, okay. Okay. Let me from beginning.
Hey. 3 2 1
foreign.
be.
[gasps]
Oh my god, that was nice. I did so
I made a mistake though. the especially
this line.
Yeah, this line.
I got that line.
It's so short.
Hi.
Then comes the the
Fore
guy
that line to mother.
Call
a guy a
guy.
I'm I'm glad there's like kanji here and
hagana [laughter]
here so I can kind of read it.
I can't do that. I [laughter] can't.
>> [sighs]
>> Okay, let's start from the song.
I'm waiting some water.
She doesn't care.
She
be
Fore
guy.
Okay. The thingy.
>> [singing]
>> My goch.
need.
Oh, wait.
[singing]
Oh, it's a long note. Okay. Okay.
Oh god, I can do this.
So um
so in the lyrics now
verse two is hard chorus uh and refrain
and verse one refrain chorus all of this
I I think I can do
>> [laughter]
>> It's hard. Bridge. I can do it. Bridge.
I can do it. Bridge. I can do it. Verse
two.
Hana. Wait, wait, wait. I think I can
read it from here.
Rooney,
that
is a vocal warm up. Yeah, that's
something I always skip. [laughter]
That's something I always get.
I always get that man.
>> [clears throat]
>> Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I want to
see if is there a off walker for
m I want
uh
I I'll look into this m um
off.
It was a beard.
Oh, if I can do this then it'll nice.
Okay.
No, you know,
but
that's a hard thing.
Should I do this? [laughter]
I think I can do this.
Oh, there it is. There it is.
Okay. Okay, we can do this. Yeah,
[laughter]
I'll just I'll use it at warm up. Okay,
I'll use his ass warm up.
Fore!
Foreign! Foreign!
skin.
Oh my god, I died.
You need to find your own vocal lens.
Yeah, I need to do that.
Is that all self-study? Uh, I need to go
to a teacher one day.
Three, two,
Fore
speech.
That's a
I'm dying. [laughter]
Last was [clears throat]
>> [gasps]
>> Is it back? Is it back? Is YouTube back?
Is YouTube back? Okay, it's back. It's
back. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Uh,
piano arrangement. Funny.
Oh.
[laughter]
Wait, I want to do this. I want to do
this. I want to do this. What the? What
the
he?
I want to do this.
Okay. Three, two, one.
foreign
>> [singing]
>> I made a mistake there. No.
[singing]
Fore!
Foreign! Foreign!
for
the stupid Good job.
Okay.
YouTube
YouTube.
I think this is a good video. I'll watch
it add to playlist.
Oh, there's a piano version for this in
there.
I need
also I just realized something. The
stream
Oh my god.
YouTube doesn't like me.
Okay, it's back. [laughter]
I'm I feel so sad to those who are
watching from YouTube.
Uh
yeah, yeah, yeah, I can read kanji a
little bit now.
Come I'm bish on it.
So
Hello mad. Dogs racer. Welcome. Welcome.
Welcome.
Okay, one second. My P is struggling
and
uh this is bad.
I want to just do the stream more. How I
doing though? I'm doing good.
A bit tired now, but I have to wrap the
stream up in a few minutes and have my
lunch.
Yeah, I've been having issues with
YouTube. It's like disconnecting my
feed.
show you. It is such a pain sometimes.
[singing]
YouTube not in receiving enough video.
N why why why are you not receiving
what
yeah next stream now I'll have to fix
all of this
somehow happy new year yeah happy new
year to you as well Mad Dog
happy new year to you as Well,
hope this year goes well for you as
well.
Uh,
okay. It's It's going to be It's already
2 hours now. So, we'll wrap it up here.
And I'm having technical difficulties,
but it is what it is. It was a gorilla
stream. It was a unplanned
stream for today. Um, yeah. Hope you
enjoyed.
Thank you to those who came by today. It
really means a lot.
Oh my god. You two, please let me do my
ending. Please don't die.
I have to report this bug, man. What
else? I have to switch my multi
streaming plat this thing. So ser
service.
Oh my god, it's it's going live stream
offline every two seconds. [laughter]
Anyway, thank you for all who came by
today. Um, it was really fun. Really,
really fun.
Hope you all enjoyed. Enjoy. Take care
and have fun everyone.
Hi. See you guys in the next stream. Uh,
probably I'll try to stream after
tonight like later today. I can't
promise. Oh, it's it it's going to be
unexpected again. Um, yeah, keep a look
out.
Keep a look out.
Either tonight or uh tomorrow, same
time, 10 a.m. or something. We'll do a
short stream. Yeah. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Hey. Anyway,
I will leave.
You guys have a good one. Bye-bye.
For those who are on YouTube, you'll be
redirected to my VOD channel for my
24hour of jock stuff.
Oh my